// Question Types
// 1. MCQs | Multiple Choice | single
// 2. boolean | true/false | single
// 3. MAQs | Multiple Answers | multiple

import { Topic } from '.'

export const generalKnowledge: Topic = {
  topic: 'GeneralKnowledge',
  level: 'Beginner',
  totalQuestions: 100,
  totalScore: 1000,
  totalTime: 100,
  questions: [

    {
      question: `''She _____ playing in the garden.''`,
      
      choices: ['were', 'was', 'is', 'are'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['was'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Roman numeral for 59?',
      
      choices: ['LIX', 'LVIII', 'XLIX', 'LXI'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['LIX'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Simplify: (8 + 2) × 5',
      
      choices: ['10', '40', '50', '30'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['50'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Correct spelling?',
      
      choices: ['Recieve', 'Receive', 'Recive', 'Receeve'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Receive'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Roman numeral for 59?',
      
      choices: ['LIX', 'LVIII', 'XLIX', 'LXI'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['LIX'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `''She _____ playing in the garden.''`,
      
      choices: ['were', 'was', 'is', 'are'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['was'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `'Antonym of 'Dark'?'`,
      
      choices: ['Light', 'Bright', 'Gloomy', 'Shadow'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Light'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Simplify: (8 + 2) × 5',
      
      choices: ['10', '40', '50', '30'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['50'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: '3/5 + 2/5 = ?',
      
      choices: ['1', '3/5', '5/10', '5/5'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['5/5'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'x + 15 = 30, find x',
      
      choices: ['30', '10', '15', '25'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['15'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `''She _____ playing in the garden.''`,
      
      choices: ['were', 'was', 'is', 'are'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['was'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Convert 2.5 kg to grams.',
      
      choices: ['250g', '2500g', '25g', '2.5g'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['2500g'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'x + 15 = 30, find x',
      
      choices: ['30', '10', '15', '25'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['15'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Roman numeral for 59?',
      
      choices: ['LIX', 'LVIII', 'XLIX', 'LXI'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['LIX'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `'Past tense of 'goes'?'`,
      
      choices: ['gone', 'went', 'going', 'go'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['went'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Area of rectangle (10 cm × 4 cm)?',
      
      choices: ['14', '40', '20', '100'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['40'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Simplify: (8 + 2) × 5',
      
      choices: ['10', '40', '50', '30'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['50'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `''____ apple a day...''`,
      
      choices: ['A', 'The', 'An', 'No article'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['An'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `'Synonym of 'Brave'?'`,
      
      choices: ['Coward', 'Fearless', 'Weak', 'None'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Fearless'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'What is 25% of 200?',
      
      choices: ['25', '50', '75', '100'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['50'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Seconds in 2 hours?',
      
      choices: ['120', '7200', '3600', '1800'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['7200'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Area of rectangle (10 cm × 4 cm)?',
      
      choices: ['14', '40', '20', '100'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['40'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Square of 9?',
      
      choices: ['81', '18', '27', '72'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['81'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: '3/5 + 2/5 = ?',
      
      choices: ['1', '3/5', '5/10', '5/5'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['5/5'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `'Rearrange: 'quickly / the / ran / dog''`,
      
      choices: ['The dog quickly ran', 'The quickly ran dog', 'Dog the quickly ran', 'The dog ran quickly'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['The dog ran quickly'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Convert 2.5 kg to grams.',
      
      choices: ['250g', '2500g', '25g', '2.5g'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['2500g'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `'Rearrange: 'quickly / the / ran / dog''`,
      
      choices: ['The dog quickly ran', 'The quickly ran dog', 'Dog the quickly ran', 'The dog ran quickly'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['The dog ran quickly'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Correct spelling?',
      
      choices: ['Recieve', 'Receive', 'Recive', 'Receeve'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Receive'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'x + 15 = 30, find x',
      
      choices: ['30', '10', '15', '25'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['15'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `''____ apple a day...''`,
      
      choices: ['A', 'The', 'An', 'No article'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['An'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `'Adjective in: 'The tall boy won.'?'`,
      
      choices: ['boy', 'tall', 'won', 'The'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['tall'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `'Verb in: 'The dog barked loudly.'?'`,
      
      choices: ['The', 'Dog', 'Barked', 'Loudly'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Barked'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'What is 25% of 200?',
      
      choices: ['25', '50', '75', '100'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['50'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `'Type of sentence: 'Please help me.''`,
      
      choices: ['Exclamatory', 'Declarative', 'Interrogative', 'Imperative'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Imperative'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `'Synonym of 'Brave'?'`,
      
      choices: ['Coward', 'Fearless', 'Weak', 'None'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Fearless'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `''____ apple a day...''`,
      
      choices: ['A', 'The', 'An', 'No article'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['An'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Area of rectangle (10 cm × 4 cm)?',
      
      choices: ['14', '40', '20', '100'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['40'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: '3/5 + 2/5 = ?',
      
      choices: ['1', '3/5', '5/10', '5/5'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['5/5'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'What is 25% of 200?',
      
      choices: ['25', '50', '75', '100'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['50'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Find the LCM of 8 and 12.',
      
      choices: ['24', '12', '8', '48'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['24'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `'Type of sentence: 'Please help me.''`,
      
      choices: ['Exclamatory', 'Declarative', 'Interrogative', 'Imperative'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Imperative'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `'Rearrange: 'quickly / the / ran / dog''`,
      
      choices: ['The dog quickly ran', 'The quickly ran dog', 'Dog the quickly ran', 'The dog ran quickly'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['The dog ran quickly'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Find the LCM of 8 and 12.',
      
      choices: ['24', '12', '8', '48'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['24'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Find the LCM of 8 and 12.',
      
      choices: ['24', '12', '8', '48'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['24'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `'Past tense of 'goes'?'`,
      
      choices: ['gone', 'went', 'going', 'go'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['went'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `''____ apple a day...''`,
      
      choices: ['A', 'The', 'An', 'No article'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['An'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `'Rearrange: 'quickly / the / ran / dog''`,
      
      choices: ['The dog quickly ran', 'The quickly ran dog', 'Dog the quickly ran', 'The dog ran quickly'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['The dog ran quickly'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Convert 2.5 kg to grams.',
      
      choices: ['250g', '2500g', '25g', '2.5g'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['2500g'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Seconds in 2 hours?',
      
      choices: ['120', '7200', '3600', '1800'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['7200'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `'Past tense of 'goes'?'`,
      
      choices: ['gone', 'went', 'going', 'go'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['went'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `''____ apple a day...''`,
      
      choices: ['A', 'The', 'An', 'No article'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['An'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Roman numeral for 59?',
      
      choices: ['LIX', 'LVIII', 'XLIX', 'LXI'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['LIX'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `'Past tense of 'goes'?'`,
      
      choices: ['gone', 'went', 'going', 'go'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['went'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Correct spelling?',
      
      choices: ['Recieve', 'Receive', 'Recive', 'Receeve'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Receive'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Area of rectangle (10 cm × 4 cm)?',
      
      choices: ['14', '40', '20', '100'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['40'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `'Past tense of 'goes'?'`,
      
      choices: ['gone', 'went', 'going', 'go'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['went'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Area of rectangle (10 cm × 4 cm)?',
      
      choices: ['14', '40', '20', '100'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['40'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Square of 9?',
      
      choices: ['81', '18', '27', '72'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['81'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `'Verb in: 'The dog barked loudly.'?'`,
      
      choices: ['The', 'Dog', 'Barked', 'Loudly'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Barked'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `'Rearrange: 'quickly / the / ran / dog''`,
      
      choices: ['The dog quickly ran', 'The quickly ran dog', 'Dog the quickly ran', 'The dog ran quickly'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['The dog ran quickly'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `'Synonym of 'Brave'?'`,
      
      choices: ['Coward', 'Fearless', 'Weak', 'None'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Fearless'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'What is 25% of 200?',
      
      choices: ['25', '50', '75', '100'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['50'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Seconds in 2 hours?',
      
      choices: ['120', '7200', '3600', '1800'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['7200'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: '3/5 + 2/5 = ?',
      
      choices: ['1', '3/5', '5/10', '5/5'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['5/5'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `'Verb in: 'The dog barked loudly.'?'`,
      
      choices: ['The', 'Dog', 'Barked', 'Loudly'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Barked'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Simplify: (8 + 2) × 5',
      
      choices: ['10', '40', '50', '30'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['50'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `'Antonym of 'Dark'?'`,
      
      choices: ['Light', 'Bright', 'Gloomy', 'Shadow'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Light'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Square of 9?',
      
      choices: ['81', '18', '27', '72'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['81'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Square of 9?',
      
      choices: ['81', '18', '27', '72'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['81'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Correct spelling?',
      
      choices: ['Recieve', 'Receive', 'Recive', 'Receeve'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Receive'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Correct spelling?',
      
      choices: ['Recieve', 'Receive', 'Recive', 'Receeve'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Receive'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'x + 15 = 30, find x',
      
      choices: ['30', '10', '15', '25'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['15'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `'Verb in: 'The dog barked loudly.'?'`,
      
      choices: ['The', 'Dog', 'Barked', 'Loudly'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Barked'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'What is 25% of 200?',
      
      choices: ['25', '50', '75', '100'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['50'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `''She _____ playing in the garden.''`,
      
      choices: ['were', 'was', 'is', 'are'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['was'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `'Antonym of 'Dark'?'`,
      
      choices: ['Light', 'Bright', 'Gloomy', 'Shadow'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Light'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Simplify: (8 + 2) × 5',
      
      choices: ['10', '40', '50', '30'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['50'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Roman numeral for 59?',
      
      choices: ['LIX', 'LVIII', 'XLIX', 'LXI'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['LIX'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `'Type of sentence: 'Please help me.''`,
      
      choices: ['Exclamatory', 'Declarative', 'Interrogative', 'Imperative'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Imperative'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `'Type of sentence: 'Please help me.''`,
      
      choices: ['Exclamatory', 'Declarative', 'Interrogative', 'Imperative'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Imperative'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Simplify: (8 + 2) × 5',
      
      choices: ['10', '40', '50', '30'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['50'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `'Verb in: 'The dog barked loudly.'?'`,
      
      choices: ['The', 'Dog', 'Barked', 'Loudly'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Barked'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Seconds in 2 hours?',
      
      choices: ['120', '7200', '3600', '1800'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['7200'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `''____ apple a day...''`,
      
      choices: ['A', 'The', 'An', 'No article'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['An'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Convert 2.5 kg to grams.',
      
      choices: ['250g', '2500g', '25g', '2.5g'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['2500g'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Roman numeral for 59?',
      
      choices: ['LIX', 'LVIII', 'XLIX', 'LXI'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['LIX'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `'Synonym of 'Brave'?'`,
      
      choices: ['Coward', 'Fearless', 'Weak', 'None'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Fearless'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `'Past tense of 'goes'?'`,
      
      choices: ['gone', 'went', 'going', 'go'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['went'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Square of 9?',
      
      choices: ['81', '18', '27', '72'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['81'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `'Adjective in: 'The tall boy won.'?'`,
      
      choices: ['boy', 'tall', 'won', 'The'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['tall'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `'Type of sentence: 'Please help me.''`,
      
      choices: ['Exclamatory', 'Declarative', 'Interrogative', 'Imperative'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Imperative'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `'Synonym of 'Brave'?'`,
      
      choices: ['Coward', 'Fearless', 'Weak', 'None'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Fearless'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `''She _____ playing in the garden.''`,
      
      choices: ['were', 'was', 'is', 'are'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['was'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'What is 25% of 200?',
      
      choices: ['25', '50', '75', '100'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['50'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `''She _____ playing in the garden.''`,
      
      choices: ['were', 'was', 'is', 'are'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['was'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'x + 15 = 30, find x',
      
      choices: ['30', '10', '15', '25'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['15'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: 'Correct spelling?',
      
      choices: ['Recieve', 'Receive', 'Recive', 'Receeve'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Receive'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `'Synonym of 'Brave'?'`,
      
      choices: ['Coward', 'Fearless', 'Weak', 'None'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Fearless'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `'Type of sentence: 'Please help me.''`,
      
      choices: ['Exclamatory', 'Declarative', 'Interrogative', 'Imperative'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Imperative'],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: `'Rearrange: 'quickly / the / ran / dog''`,
      
      choices: ['The dog quickly ran', 'The quickly ran dog', 'Dog the quickly ran', 'The dog ran quickly'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['The dog ran quickly'],
      score: 10,
    },
  ],
}
